[
    {"question":" ____ what did Jimmi Hendrix play his guitar, left handed or right handed?","answer":"Witch","answer2":"Left handed"},
    {"question":"How many Oscars Joan ____ Crawford win?","answer":"did","answer2":"One"},
    {"question":"Which feature ____ common to Emmenthal and Gruyere cheeses?","answer":"is","answer2":"Holes"},
    {"question":"What metric measurement was originally defined as a ten millionth of the distance ____ the equator to the pole?","answer":"from","answer2":"Metre"},
    {"question":" ____ area of Paris was the setting of the film  'Can - Can' ?","answer":"What","answer2":"Monmartre"},
    {"question":"What is the most common language ____ in Algeria?","answer":"spoken","answer2":"Arabic"},
    {"question":"Which European capital city did Ernest Hemmingway refer to____ 'the capital of the world' ?","answer":"as","answer2":"Madrid"},
    {"question":"Which two of the four evangelists were ____ apostles?","answer":"also","answer2":"Matthew and John"},
    {"question":"Which Asian leader was in prison when time magazine named ____ man of the year for 1930?","answer":"him","answer2":"Mahatma Gandhi"},
    {"question":"What is a Gametophobic bachelor afraid ____ ?","answer":"of","answer2":"Marriage"},
    {"question":"Chives are the cousin of ____ vegetable?","answer":"which","answer2":"Onions"},
    {"question":"What is the ____ in this sequence: Alpha, beta, gamma, delta...?","answer":"next","answer2":"Epsilon"},
    {"question":"What is the ____ name of Mary Shelley's tragic hero Baron Frankenstein ?","answer":"first","answer2":"Victor"},
    {"question":"Which famous ____ sculptor created  The Thinker and  The Kiss?","answer":"French","answer2":"Aguste Rodin"},
    {"question":"Emperor Shahjahan's monument to his favorite wife ____ completed in Agra in 1563. What is it ?","answer":"was","answer2":"Taj Mahal"},
    {"question":"Which Barcelona ____ designed many distinctive buildings including the church of the Sagrada Familia ?","sanswer":"architect","answer2":"Antonio Gaudi"},
    {"question":"The herb 'wild marjoram' is ____ known by what name ?","answer":"better","answer2":"Oregano"},
    {"question":"What was Pedro Duque the first ____ to do ?","answer":"Spaniard","answer2":"Go into Space"},
    {"question":"The Boston Tea Party contributed to the ____ of which war ?","answer":"star","answer2":"American independence"},
    {"question":"____ what film has Al Pacino won his only Oscar ?","answer":"For","answer2":"The Scent Of A Woman"}
 ]